Guide to the Mario and Ruth Chamlee Collection
Stanford Archive of Recorded Sound
Mario and Ruth Chamlee Collection
1911-1977
ARS-0003
Mario Chamlee
Ruth Chamlee
17 boxes +
Stanford Archive of Recorded Sound Stanford University Libraries Stanford, California 94305-3076
The collection consists of correspondence dealing with the Metropolitan Opera Regional Auditions; personal papers, mainly promotional documents, and biographical and/or pedagogical writings; newspaper and magazine clippings; annotated scores, programs, photos, scrapbooks and recordings.
Access
Collection is open for research. Listening appointments may require 24 hours notice. Contact the Archive Operations Manager.
Biography / Administrative History
Mario Chamlee (1892-1966), tenor, was born in Los Angeles, May 29, 1892. His original name was Archer Cholmondeley. He first studied voice with Achille Alberti in Los Angeles, and later with Sibella and Dellera in New York. He made his debut in his native city in 1916 as Edgardo in Lucia di Lammermoor. A year later Mr. Chamlee went on tour with the Aborn Opera company where he sang with soprano Ruth Miller who in 1919 became his wife. With his two-year military service, during World War I, his singing career came practically to a total halt. Upon his return to the US in 1919, however, Mr. Chamlee devoted himself to developing his operatic talent. Engagements followed with various opera companies in the US, the Scotti, Metropolitan, Ravinia summer opera in Chicago, San Francisco, and in Europe. Perhaps his most acclaimed appearance was in Henri Rabaud's Marouf at the Paris Opera. Mario Chamlee retired from the opera stage at the age of 47. He subsequently devoted himself to singing popular songs, taking part in talk shows such as Tony and Gus, and teaching voice together with his wife. He recorded exclusively for Brunswick records.
Ruth Miller (1892-1983), soprano, was born in Portland Oregon on July 1, 1892. She studied in Paris with Lloyd d'Aubigne, Emile Bourgeois and Giovanni Sbriglia. She sang as lyrical and coloratura soprano, under the name of Francesca Milena, in various French and Spanish theaters starting in 1912. Her American debut was in 1917 with the Aborn opera company where she sang with baritone Richard Bonneli and tenor Mario Chamlee. She sang only one season with the Metropolitan opera (1917), appearing as Musetta in La Boheme. After marrying Mario Chamlee in 1919 she gave up her operatic career, and dedicated herself to teaching. Among her most successful students is the baritone Theodor Uppman. Examples of her singing appeared between 1940-54 under the IRCC label.
Scope and Content of Collection
Includes correspondence dealing with the Metropolitan Opera Regional Auditions; personal papers which consist of promotional documents, and biographical and/or pedagogical writings; newspaper and magazine clippings; 22 annotated scores; 7 programs; about 350 photographs, 12 scrapbooks, 285 transcription discs, 3 test pressings, 49 commercial discs, 19 reel to reel tapes and 1 cassette.
Arrangement
Organized into 9 series: I. Correspondence. II. Personal Papers. III. Newspaper and Magazine Clippings. IV. Scores. V. Programs. VI. Photographs. VII. Scrapbooks. VIII. Recordings. IX. Miscellaneous.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Chamlee, Mario, 1892-1966.; Miller, Ruth, 1892-1983.; Operas--Excerpts.; Songs (High voice); Live sound recordings.
Container List
- Correspondence
  - 1958/59 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1930-1977 (Box 1)
- Documents
  - Promotional pamphlets (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Press book (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Autobiography: Run Boy Run (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Essays: The Tenor; La Traviata; La Boheme (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Ruth's certificates (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Teaching materials (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - National Association of Teachers of Singing (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1959/60 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1962-64 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Documents: Judging forms, applications (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Newspaper and magazine clippings
  - Newspaper and Magazine Clippings 1922-1976 (Box 2)
    The Chamlees gathered the vast majority of their clippings in scrapbooks, therefore their collection of loose newspaper and magazine clippings is rather small. Among the twelve clippings are those of the Ravinia summer season of 1937; the Scotti opera's tour in 1921; the Detriot opera production of Manon of 1934 in which Mario sang the role of des Griuex; and on a quite different plane an article entitled "Battle of the Sexes" of 1937 in which Mario gives, in an interview, his definitions of the "model mate."
- Scores
  - Annotated scores collected by Ruth Miller Chamlee (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Canteloube, Joseph, 1879-1957. Chants d'Auvergne -- Chausson, Ernest, 1855-1899. Chanson perpétuelle -- Hart, Fritz Bennicke, 1874-1949 -- Marx, Joseph, 1882-1964. Lieder und Gesänge. Valse de Chopin -- Poulenc, Francis, 1899-1963. Airs chantés -- Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. Romansy, op. 4. V molchan'i nochi tainoi -- Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. Romansy, op. 14. Ne ver' mne, drug -- Ravel, Maurice, 1875-1937. Shéhérazade (Song cycle) -- Rimsky-Korsakov, Nikolay, 1844-1908. Snegurochka. Pesen' Lelia -- Schaffer, Laura. Four Songs -- Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Lieder, op. 41. Wiegenlied -- Debussy, Claude, 1862-1918. Ariettes oubliées. Chevaux de bois -- Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Wesendonck-Lieder -- Photocopies of unidentified Cavatina.
  - Annotated scores collected by Mario Chamlee (Othertype 2, Folder 2)
    Buzzi-Peccia, Arturo, 1854-1943 Five Italian Songs -- De Crescenzo, Vincenzo, 1875-1964. Blanquita -- Falvo, R. Bolero D'Amore -- Gambardella, S. (Salvatore), 1873-1913 Canzoni Napolitane. O Surdato Napulitano!; Tagliaferri, Ernesto, 1889-1937. Tarantella Internazionale; Tanara, Fernando. Two Venetian Dialect Songs.
- Programs
  - Programs 1925-1976 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    The program collection is made up of 7 items ranging from 1925 to 1976. Some are of performances of their students, such as that of Richard Kendall Buchwitz.
  - Art work: watercolor and print on cloth (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Children's book "Keep on singing" (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Mario's Brunswick disc sleeve (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Cleopatra booklet (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Annotated scores collected by Mario Chamlee: Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Messa da Requiem (Othertype 3, Folder 3)
    With an inscription by Ruth M. Chamlee: "The phrasing in this book is all that of Toscanini in preparation for this performance of January 15, 1931." Toscanini, Arturo, 1867-1957
  - Annotated scores collected by Mario Chamlee: Auber, D. F. E. (Daniel François Esprit), 1782-1871. Fra Diavolo (Othertype 3, Folder 4)
- Photographs
  - Unidentified roles (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - As Don Jose. Bizet, Georges, 1838-1875. Carmen (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - As Caponsacchi. Hageman, Richard, 1882-1966. Caponsacchi (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - As Paglerino. Leoncavallo, Ruggiero, 1858-1919. Pagliacci (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - As Turiddu. Mascagni, Pietro, 1863-1945. Cavalleria rusticana (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - As de Grieux. Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Manon (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - As Tamino. Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Zauberflöte (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - As Hoffmann. Offenbach, Jacques, 1819-1880. Contes d'Hoffmann (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - As Rodolfo. Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Bohe`me (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - As Pinkerton. Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Madama Butterfly (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - As Cavaradossi. Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Tosca (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - As Mârouf. Rabaud, Henri, 1873-1949. Mârouf, savetier du Caire (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - As Almaviva. Rossini, Gioacchino, 1792-1868. Barbiere di Siviglia (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - As Samson. Saint-Saëns, Camille, 1835-1921. Samson et Dalila (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - As Hans. Smetana, Bedrich, 1824-1884. Prodaná nevêsta (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - As Rigoletto and Duke of Mantua. Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Rigoletto (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - As Alfredo. Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Traviata (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Ruth and Mario in Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Manon (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Mario singing off-stage; Recording session at the Sorbonne; Special occasions (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Scrapbooks
  - Scrapbook, 11.5" x 9.5" Blue covers with metal spiral. Title: Photo Album. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    First entry: French Visa entry document. "Laissez-Passer" Dated January 3, 1911.
  - Scrapbook, 11.5" x 9.5" Red covers with metal spiral. Title: Photo Album. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    First entry: Royal Albert Hall announcement. June 3, 19??. First appearance of a year 1933.
  - Scrapbook, 16" x 11" Green covers with title "Scrap Book." Bound. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    First entry: black and white photo of Mario Chamlee in military uniform, with a dedication, dated 1918. Microfilmed: at the end of reel #1.
  - Scrapbook, 14" x 10" Black covers, with red spine and corners, no title. Bound. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    First entry: Ravinia Season Program: 1930, June 21 -September 1. Microfilmed beginning of reel #2.
  - Scrapbook, 11.5" x 9.5" Red covers with metal spiral. Title: Photo Album. (Box 9, Folder 9)
    First entry: Certificate of Recognition awarded to Mario Chamlee from the Los Angeles Area U.S.O. Board. June 14, 1944. Treated by Preservation, materials in folders.
  - Scrapbook, 10.5" x 9" One green cover. (Box 9, Folder 10)
    First insert: National Association of Teachers of Singing. 1944-1969. On the occasion of the Silver Jubilee Convention. Treated by A. Castillo, materials in folders
  - Scrapbook, Unknown size. Album items in folders, treated by preservation. (Box 9, Folder 12)
    All items pertaining to Mezzo-Soprano Belva Kibler. Relation to the Chamlee collection is unknown. First date: 1927
  - Scrapbook, Empty scrapbook lined with hand painted paper. (Box 10, Folder 13)
    First date: 1927
  - Scrapbook, Empty scrapbook lined with hand painted paper. (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Recordings
  - Mario singing songs and arias, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips, half-track, mono.; 7 in. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Side 1: Sometimes between long shadows (absent) -- When you came to the end of a perfect day -- Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Elégie -- Who knows -- Mascagni, Pietro, 1863-1945. Cavalleria rusticana. O Lola -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Rigoletto. Questa o quella per me pari sono -- Flotow, Friedrich von, 1812-1883. Martha -- Your eyes have told me -- Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Tosca. Recondita armonia; E lucevan le stelle -- Thank God for a garden -- Dreams of long ago -- Oh holy night -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Rigoletto. Donna é mobile -- Marcheta -- Memory Lane -- Geehl, Henry Ernest, 1881-1961. For you alone -- Dreams of long ago -- I dream of the day I met you -- Tosti, F. Paolo (Francesco Paolo), 1846-1916. Parted -- Buzzi-Peccia, Arturo, 1854-1943. Lolita -- Tosti, F. Paolo (Francesco Paolo), 1846-1916. Mattinata -- Come where the moon -- Old refrain -- Berceuse -- Paquita -- Indian Lullaby -- Mi niña -- Where are you -- Mother oh my mother -- I look into your garden. Side 2: Give me a rose to remember -- Only a rose -- Here in my arms -- O lovely night -- There is a place in my heart -- Come onto him (duet with John Thomas) -- The last chord -- Forgotten -- Last night I was dreaming -- Even as the flower -- Dearest, do not chide me -- On yonder (?) -- Then you'll remember -- I dream of the day I met you -- Tosti, F. Paolo (Francesco Paolo), 1846-1916. Parted -- Di Capua, Eduardo, 1864-1917. O sole mio -- Santa Lucia -- Meyerbeer, Giacomo, 1791-1864. Africaine. O paradis sorti de l'onde -- Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Manon. En fermant les yeux je vois -- Your voice (?) -- Call me no more -- Dreams dimly lying -- Out of the dusk -- Moon dream shore -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Trovatore. Sì, la stanchezza; Mal reggendo all'aspro assalto -- Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Tosca. E lucevan le stelle -- Dreams of long ago.
  - Mario singing songs and arias, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, half-track, mono.; 7 in. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    From the collection of Knox P. Walker.Side 1: Williams; Quirke. Your voice -- Eberhart; Cadman. Call me no more -- Cadman -- Godard, Benjamin, 1849-1895. Jocelyn. Berceuse -- Buzzi-Peccia, Arturo, 1854-1943. Paquita -- Herbert, Victor, 1859-1924. Dream girl. My dream girl -- Brown; Spencer. Me Neenya -- Faure, J. (Jean), 1830-1914. Crucifix -- (with Thomas John Charles, 1945-) -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Trovatore. Sì, la stanchezza from Trovatore (electric recording); Mal reggendo all' aspro assalto (electric recording) -- Buzzi-Peccia, Arturo, 1854-1943. Paquita -- (electric recording) -- Tosti, F. Paolo (Francesco Paolo), 1846-1916. Ideale -- Silver threads among the gold (Walter Hammond &Male Qt.) -- Bizet, Georges, 1838-1875. Carmen. Fleur que tu m'avais jetée -- Side 2: Lehmann, Liza, 1862-1918. In a Persian garden. Ah, moon of my delight -- Stewart; Dorel. When my ships come sailing home -- Flotow, Friedrich von, 1812-1883. Martha. Ja, seit früher Kindheit -- (with Richard Bonneli. Electric reocrding) -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Forza del destino. Solenne in quest' ora (with Richard Bonneli) -- Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Il se fait tard -- (duet with Florence Easton. Electric) -- Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Tosca. Recondita armonia (electric recording) -- Ponchielli, Amilcare, 1834-1886. Gioconda. Cielo e mar (electric recording).
  - Mario singing songs and arias, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, half-track, mono.; 7 in. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    (Long blank at beginning of tape) -- Ave Maria -- Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Bohème. Che gelida manina.
  - Mario singing songs and arias, April 6, 1963., 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, half-track, mono.; 7 in. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Dubbed from discs. Tosti, F. Paolo (Francesco Paolo), 1846-1916. Canzoni di Amaranta. Alba separa dalla luce l'ombra -- Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Tosca. Recondita armonia -- Leoncavallo, Ruggiero, 1858-1919. Pagliacci. Vesti la giubba -- Siciliana -- Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Manon. En fermant les yeux je vois -- Meyerbeer, Giacomo, 1791-1864. Africaine. O paradis sorti de l'onde -- Thomas, Ambroise, 1811-1896. Mignon. De son coeur j'ai calmé -- Elegie -- De Ferrari, Serafino, 1824-1885. Pipelet. Questa notte mentre a letto- Lehmann, Liza, 1862-1918. In a Persian garden. Ah, moon of my delight -- Out of the dusk to you -- Verdi, Giuseppe,1813-1901. Forza del destino.
  - Mario singing songs and arias, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, half-track, mono.; 7 in. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    Memory lane -- Marcheta -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Trovatore. Sì, la stanchezza ;Mal reggendo all'aspro assalto -- Red rose -- Here in your arms its adorable -- Dreams of flong ago -- Take thou this rose -- Santa Lucia -- Di Capua, Eduardo, 1864-1917. O sole mio -- Dreams dimly lying -- The last hour -- The last refrain --Moonlight -- Call me no more -- Your voice -- Look into your garden -- Give me one rose to remember -- Now love is mine -- M' appari -- Oh holy night -- Stars are gleaming.
  - Smetana's The Bartered Bride I, May 8, 1937., 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, half-track, mono.; 7 in. (Box 11, Folder 6)
    From the Metropolitan Opera House. Performers: Pelletier, Wilfrid, 1896-1982, conductor; Chamlee, Mario as Hans; Bodanya, Natalie as Esmeralda; Burke, Hilda as Marie; Cordon, Norman as Springer; Gurney, John as Micha; Engelman, Wilfred as Kruscina.Smetana, Bedrich, 1824-1884. Prodaná nevesta.
  - Smetana's The Bartered Bride II, May 8, 1937., 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, half-track, mono.; 7 in. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - World of Opera., 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, half-track, mono.; 7 in. (Box 11, Folder 8)
    KFAC. Carl Princi, host.Royal Opera HousePerformers: Henry, Leigh (sp?), conductor; Horne, Marilyn, soprano.Meyerbeer, Giacomo, 1791-1864. Huguenots. Rome Orchestra Performers: Morel, Jean, 1903-1975, conductor; Tozzi, Giorgio, bass.Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Simon Boccanegra. Lacerato spirito
  - World of Opera, Nov. 25, 1964, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, half-track, mono.; 5 in. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    KFAC. Carl Princi, host.Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Manon. En fermant les yeux je vois -- Interview with Chamlee, Mario.
  - World of Opera -- Chamlee's rehearsing., 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, half-track, mono.; 5 in. (Box 11, Folder 10)
    KFAC. Carl Princi, host.Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Don Pasquale. Com'è gentil -- Rehearsal with Chamlee, Mario, piano and Chamlee, Ruth (?), voice. Songs in English.
  - Mario Chamlee's lecture on tenors, 1966., 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, half-track, mono.; 5 in. (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Workshop, NATS Victoria B.C.
  - Martin Bernheimer interviews Mario Chamlee, Oct. 11, 1960., 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, half-track, mono.; 5 in. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Saturday Opera, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, half-track, mono.; 7 in. (Box 11, Folder 13)
    Side 1: KOGO FM. Interview with Mario Chamlee from around 1950.Side 2: KOGO FM. From an acoustic recording in 1924Mascagni, Pietro, 1863-1945. Cavalleria rusticana. Siciliana; Brindisi -- Smetana, Bedrich, 1824-1884. Prodaná nevesta. Oh my adored one.
  - Mario's autobiography, Run Boy Run., 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, half-track, mono.; 5 in. (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Interview with Mario Chamlee on his autobiography. With participation of Ruth M. Chamlee.
  - Scrapbook, Unknown size. Scrap Book lost, content filmed. At the beginning of microfilm #1. First entry: Photo of Mario Chamlee in the Musical Observer, no date. First appearance of complete date: Oct.14,1925. (Box 12, Folder 11)
    First date: 1925
  - Mario's autobiography, Run Boy Run. Part I, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, half-track, mono.; 5 in. (Box 12, Folder 15)
    Ruth M. Chamlee reads from Mario Chamlee's autobiography.
  - Mario's autobiography, Run Boy Run. Part II, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, half-track, mono.; 5 in. (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Ruth M. Chamlee lecture at the L.A. Chapter of NATS, Feb. 7, 1965., 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, half-track, mono.; 7 in. (Box 12, Folder 17)
    The History of the Art of Singing. (Recorded on one side only, tape has multiple splices).
  - Metropolitan Farewell Gala Performance, April 16, 1966., 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips, half-track, mono.; 7 in. (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - World of Opera: Tribute to Mario Chamlee, Nov.16, 1966., 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, half-track, mono.; 7 in. (Box 12, Folder 19)
    Broadcast on KFAC, with Carl Princi. Thomas, Ambroise, 1811-1896. Mignon. Adieu, Mignon
  - Opera Box: Mario Chamlee., 1 sound tape cassette: stereo, 90 minutes (Box 12, Folder 1)
    KUSC program with Jim Sveda Radio. Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Manon. En fermant les yeux je vois -- Three popular songs recorded in the early 1920s: Paquita -- For you alone -- Santa Lucia.
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Apr. 29, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, alumnum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Transcription discs. Tony and Gus a daily, 15 minute, humorous and sentimental talk-show with music. Described by the announcer as an "utterly different kind of radio program" consisting of "romance and music with one of the greatest tenors of the world." Speaking is combined with Mario Cahmlee singing popular songs. Tony, "gay and romantic," and Gus, "lovable and philosophical," are two Italian fellows who arrive to the "land of opportunities"
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Apr. 29, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Apr. 29, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Apr. 29, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Apr. 29, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Apr. 30, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ) Apr. 30, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 2, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 2, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 3, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 3, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 6, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 6, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 7, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 7, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 8, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 8, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 9, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 9, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 9, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 10, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 10, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 13, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 13, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 14, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 14, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 15, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 15, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 16, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 16, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 17, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 17, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 20, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 20, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 21, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Tony &Gus (Radio program; WJZ)May 21, 1935, sound disc: 78 rpm, aluminum and acetate; 12 in. (Box 13, Folder 36)